module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which branch of the U.S. Armed Forces operates under the Department of Homeland Security during peacetime?', 
    a: 'Coast Guard',
    b: 'National Guard',
    c: 'Navy',
    d: 'Air Force',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a female pig called?', 
    a: 'Boar',
    b: 'Sow',
    c: 'Piglet',
    d: 'Swine',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What ailment does the medicine Nexium treat?', 
    a: 'Eczema',
    b: 'Flatulence',
    c: 'Impotence',
    d: 'Heartburn',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: '"Up-Up-Down-Down-Left-Right-Left-Right B, A, Start" is also known as what?', 
    a: 'The Da Vinci Code',
    b: 'The Konami Code',
    c: 'The Caesar Shift',
    d: 'RSA Encryption',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the National Mammal of the United States?', 
    a: 'Bald Eagle',
    b: 'Bison',
    c: 'Grizzly Bear',
    d: 'Dog',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which band wrote the popular stadium anthem-like song "The Final Countdown"?', 
    a: 'Van Halen',
    b: 'Bon Jovi',
    c: 'Scorpions',
    d: 'Europe',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was first American astronaut to travel into space?', 
    a: 'Buzz Aldrin',
    b: 'Neil Armstrong',
    c: 'Alan Shepard',
    d: 'Lance Armstrong',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a skateboarding trick?', 
    a: 'Snausage',
    b: 'Nollie',
    c: 'Ollie',
    d: 'Grind',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What sandwich is composed of corned beef, Swiss cheese, sauerkraut, and Russian dressing, grilled between slices of rye bread?', 
    a: 'Porchetta',
    b: 'Reuben',
    c: 'Monte Cristo',
    d: 'Cuban',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Yahoo, LinkedIn, and NetApp are all headquartered where?', 
    a: 'San Francisco, CA',
    b: 'Sunnyvale, CA',
    c: 'Palo Alto, CA',
    d: 'Redmond, WA',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];